Log in. Bleed out.
Death Streamer is a horror film directed by Charles Band.
A modern-age vampire employs technologically advanced glasses that enable him to not only hunt his victims
in and out of the virtual world...but also LIVE STREAM his bloody feasts for all to see!
As this high-tech ghoul continues to glut on his screaming victims, his internet-based
cult of personality expands, his fanbase addicted to watching the slaughter.
But when an intrepid trio of young supernatural investigators lock-down on the trail of
the "Death Streamer", the fiend turns the tables and begins stalking them.
Arturo Valenor (Unknown), played by Sean Ohlman.
Alex Jarvis, played by Aaron McDaniel.
Edwina, played by Emma Massalone.
Juniper, played by Kaitlin Moore.
Li Chun, played by Chili Jean.
Thug, played by Travis Stoner.
Kick (also known as Kick.com) is an Australian video livestreaming service.
It is operated by Kick Streaming Pty Ltd and backed by online casino
company Stake.com and streaming personality Trainwreckstv.
Kick was founded in 2022 as a competitor to Twitch, with a focus on looser moderation, higher revenue shares for
streamers, and the inclusion of online gambling content which has been banned from other platforms.
In 2023, Kick made multiple high-profile deals with
streamers including Adin Ross and xQc.
In Q3 2025, StreamCharts listed Kick.com as the fourth most watched livestreaming platform
(among those monitored by the site) behind YouTube, TikTok, and Twitch.
From 2023 until the end of 2025, Kick was also the sponsor of
the Sauber Motorsport racing team in Formula One.
The film explores themes of vampire, b movie, vampire cult, livestream.
The tone is dark.